{
    "questions": [
        {
            "languageId": 2,
            "topicId": 28,
            "level": "beginner",
            "mark": 1,
            "time": 1,
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the output of the following code snippet?",
                    "code":"\nx = 5\ny = x\nx = 10\nprint(y)",
                    "option": ["5", "10", "Error", "None"],
                    "answer": "5"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "languageId": 2,
            "topicId": 28,
            "level": "beginner",
            "mark": 1,
            "time": 1,
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Which of the following is a valid Python variable name?",
                    "code":"",
                    "option": ["2x", "_variable", "global", "class"],
                    "answer": "_variable"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "languageId": 2,
            "topicId": 28,
            "level": "beginner",
            "mark": 1,
            "time": 1,
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does the following code snippet print?",
                    "code":"\na = 5\nb = 3\nc = a * b\nprint(c)",
                    "option": ["8", "15", "53", "Error"],
                    "answer": "15"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "languageId": 2,
            "topicId": 28,
            "level": "beginner",
            "mark": 1,
            "time": 1,
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What happens when you assign multiple values to variables in Python?",
                    "code":"",
                    "option": ["Only the last assigned value is stored", "Values are stored in a tuple", "Values are stored in a list", "Each variable receives its corresponding value"],
                    "answer": "Each variable receives its corresponding value"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "languageId": 2,
            "topicId": 28,
            "level": "beginner",
            "mark": 1,
            "time": 1,
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the output of the following code?",
                    "code":"\nglobal_var = 10\n\ndef change_global():\n    global global_var\n    global_var = 20\n\nchange_global()\nprint(global_var)",
                    "option": ["10", "20", "Error", "None"],
                    "answer": "20"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "languageId": 2,
            "topicId": 28,
            "level": "beginner",
            "mark": 1,
            "time": 1,
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Which of the following is not a valid Python variable type?",
                    "code":"",
                    "option": ["int", "string", "real", "list"],
                    "answer": "real"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "languageId": 2,
            "topicId": 28,
            "level": "beginner",
            "mark": 1,
            "time": 1,
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does the following code print?",
                    "code":"\na = [1, 2, 3]\nb = a\na.append(4)\nprint(b)",
                    "option": ["[1, 2, 3]", "[1, 2, 3, 4]", "[1, 2, 4]", "Error"],
                    "answer": "[1, 2, 3, 4]"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "languageId": 2,
            "topicId": 28,
            "level": "beginner",
            "mark": 1,
            "time": 1,
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the output of the following code snippet?",
                    "code":"\nx = 5\nx += 2\nprint(x)",
                    "option": ["5", "7", "10", "Error"],
                    "answer": "7"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "languageId": 2,
            "topicId": 28,
            "level": "beginner",
            "mark": 1,
            "time": 1,
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Which of the following is a valid way to concatenate two strings in Python?",
                    "code":"",
                    "option": ["str1 .concat(str2)", "str1 + str2", "str1 .add(str2)", "str1 .append(str2)"],
                    "answer": "str1 + str2"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "languageId": 2,
            "topicId": 28,
            "level": "beginner",
            "mark": 1,
            "time": 1,
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Which of the following is a valid way to check the type of a variable in Python?",
                    "code":"",
                    "option": ["typeof(var)", "type(var)", "var.type()", "var.type"],
                    "answer": "type(var)"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "languageId": 2,
            "topicId": 28,
            "level": "beginner",
            "mark": 1,
            "time": 1,
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the output of the following code snippet?",
                    "code":"\nx = 5\ny = x\nx += 2\nprint(y)",
                    "option": ["5", "7", "(5, 7)", "Error"],
                    "answer": "5"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "languageId": 2,
            "topicId": 28,
            "level": "beginner",
            "mark": 1,
            "time": 1,
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What happens when you assign a value to a variable that has not been defined in Python?",
                    "code":"",
                    "option": ["Python creates a new variable with that name", "Error", "Python prompts the user to define the variable", "None of the above"],
                    "answer": "Error"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "languageId": 2,
            "topicId": 28,
            "level": "beginner",
            "mark": 1,
            "time": 1,
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Which of the following is a valid Python variable name?",
                    "code":"",
                    "option": ["1var", "var_1", "var-1", "var 1"],
                    "answer": "var_1"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "languageId": 2,
            "topicId": 28,
            "level": "beginner",
            "mark": 1,
            "time": 1,
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the output of the following code snippet?",
                    "code":"\na = \"Hello\"\nb = a\na += \" World\"\nprint(b)",
                    "option": ["Hello", "World", "Hello World", "Error"],
                    "answer": "Hello"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "languageId": 2,
            "topicId": 28,
            "level": "beginner",
            "mark": 1,
            "time": 1,
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the scope of a global variable in Python?",
                    "code":"",
                    "option": ["Limited to the function where it's defined", "Available throughout the entire program", "Accessible only within the class where it's defined", "Restricted to a specific module"],
                    "answer": "Available throughout the entire program"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}
